# **ROSHNI KOLI**

SAP FUNCTIONAL CONSULTANT

Indianapolis, Indiana 46237

C# +13176529847|roshni.koli@gmail.com

As my resume indicates, I possess more than 4 years of progressive experience in the SAP BI/BW HANA field. My professional history includes positions such as Senior Executive at Wipro Info Systems Pvt. Ltd. as well as Associate Software Engineer at Accenture.

Most recently, my responsibilities included Design and development of BEx queries based on Composite Providers and Multi-Providers, Performed data modelling and developed analytical views for the transactional data in HANA, Managed and prioritized SAP defects including debugging and fixing of complex problems in a timely manner. I assisted in the successful completion of Migration of HANA content from development, testing environment to Production environment using delivery units. My supervisor also relied on my ability to Analyze reports and suggest improvements in performance of existing solutions, created Technical specifications for Business and standard modelling documents for HANA.

I have attached my resume for your reference.

# ROSHNI JAYENDRA KOLI

+13176529847

## roshni.koli@gmail.com

- Experienced Functional Analyst in SAP BI and HANA with expertise in integrating SAP BI with SAP SD, SAP MM and other SAP modules and third party systems
- Development and Functional expertise on end-to-end development of SAP projects from evaluation to delivery
- Extensive SAP BW/BI, HANA knowledge design and implementation of BEx queries, ETL framework and solution architecture, design and implementation

#### **Summary**

Roshni Koli has 4 + years of functional as well as technical experience as a SAP Consultant BW 7.4 / BI / BO / HANA S/4 / ABAP having worked at multi-national organizations like Accenture Services Pvt. Ltd. and Wipro Info Systems.

2+ years of SAP HANA experience having worked on SAP HANA Studio for Data Modeling, replicating and loading tables in HANA using BODS, SLT, creating Calculation and Analytic views on the replicated tables, CE Functions and optimizing Info Cubes.

She has extensive experience in Design, Blueprint, Workshops, Data Migration, Authorization Framework Design, End User Training and Post Go-Live Support, and has considerable expertise in implementations using ASAP methodology. She has a very comprehensive understanding of SAP BI and HANA objects and processes, and demonstrated expertise in integrating SAP SD with SAP MM.

Roshni has an in-depth knowledge of SAP BI/BW and HANA architecture, design and implementation. Her experience includes the entire lifecycle of Product Development including Requirement gathering, specification, design, development, customer message handling and documentation.

Roshni has experience of implementation projects in varied industries like Gold and Copper mining, Telecom and Banking. She has good analytical and problem-solving skills and is delivery focused.

# **Work Experience**

Jul 2016 - Feb 2017 - SAP BW/BI/ABAP/BO

Wipro Info-systems - Mumbai, India

Client - HDFC Bank

Technology used: SAP BI 7.3, SAP BO 4

### Responsibilities:

- Daily monitoring BW production boxes to ensure no SLA is missed
- Proactively managed projects stakeholder satisfaction to secure customer satisfaction
- SME on Warranty Portfolio for EMEA
- SAP BOXI 4 WebI report design and integration with current system SAP BW 7.3
- Analysing reports and improve its performance
- Responsible for development of Extraction programs, Programs and FM based on SAP modules SD / MM / CS / LO
- Overall responsibility for a Customer Differentiation reporting solution
- Planning and collaboration with resources in APJ, EMEA and Americas
- Design, configuration, ETL and maintenance SI Trackers and Incident Managements
- Determine which tasks/steps to automate (by identifying scope and requirements)
- Support the SIT & UAT phases working on all defects & approved CRs for the HPS SAP Platform FI area to ensure exit on target

Jan 2015 – June 2016 - SAP Senior Consultant BW-HANA/BI/ABAP

Iken Personics - Mumbai, India

**Client - Airtel** 

Technology used: SAP BI 7.4, SAP HANA studio, NLS, BO 4

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Responsible for development of Extraction programs, Programs and FM based on SAP module SD
- Code review and improve process using the standard SAP performance guides
- Design and development of BEx queries based on Composite Providers and MultiProviders
- Performed data modelling and developed analytical views for the transactional data in HANA
- Created attribute view, analytic View and calculation view based on Data foundation and join including the refining of output structure based on project and business requirements

- Developing SQL Script for BW Transformations and HANA Calculation View
- Managed and prioritised SAP defects including debugging and fixing of complex problems in a timely manner
- Working on POC's for Sales business units using SAP HANA by following best practices and optimised data models and also had consumed these data models in MS Excel and Business Objects Explorer
- Designing and implementing solution to bring plan data from legacy JDA system into BW
- Resolving and developing solution to calculate daily status of the product life cycle within all stores across the company
- Proactively managed projects stakeholder satisfaction to secure customer satisfaction
- Support the SIT & UAT phases working on all defects & approved CRs for the HPS SAP Platform FI area to ensure quality exit on target
- Design, configuration, daily jobs control
- Integrated BOBJ 4.0 and DataStage with SAP HANA SPS12
- Migrated HANA content from development, testing environment to Production environment using delivery units
- Analysing reports and improve its performance
- SAP BW landscape has been completely re-build and optimised with an EDW / LSA++ layered structure, ABAP-OO and performance optimisation has been taken into account
- Overall responsibility for the Macro Space and Plan Data
- Planning and collaboration with resources within various teams
- Established the best modelling and recommended strategies for BOBJ environment and architecture for SAP HANA
- Created Technical specifications for Business and standard modelling documents for HANA

Oct 2011 - Jul 2013 - SAP BI/ABAP Consultant

Accenture Services Pvt. Ltd. - Bangalore, India

Client - Freeport McMoran

Technology used: SAP ABAP, BI

#### Responsibilities:

- Technical planning of data migration and Unicode conversion
- InfoCube data modelling, design and query development
- Responsible for development of Extraction Reports, Master Data Migration
- Providing technical analysis, expertise and solutions on system issues
- Developing and testing programs to technical specifications
- Maintenance in SAP FI CO and CO-PA modules (Cost Centre, Profit Centre, Vendor, Customer, Profitability Analysis)
- Business analyst, understanding the requirements and converting them into both functional and technical documents for development.
- Write functional and technical documentation

- Techno-functional SAP ABAP experience
- Proactively managed systems development, implementation and end user actions from legacy system
- Development of programs with Unicode conversion
- SAP HR Infotypes
- Translated requirements into functional and technical specifications

# **Education**

Degree / Stream	Bachelor of Engineering – Computers
Year	2011
Percentage	66.40%
Main Subjects	Computer Science, Data Mining
	Thadomal Shahani Engineering College –
University	Bandra West, Mumbai, India.
	Affiliated to Mumbai University